hi everyone this is eya on eya censored
supernatural bible changes on youtube
and today is the 25th of may
and the other day i did a video about
changes
to
the name of god and in that
long stream that i did showing you a lot
of changes
related to our creator
i covered this particular change but it
really does
deserve its own video
because we uncovered
that jesus christ
in scripture
now has his own
son
our bibles are under savage satanic
assault
and supernaturally changing and it's
time to wake up
in jesus name there's not much time
i've been covering this nefarious wicked
changes since 2016
and the changes have only accelerated
take a screenshot of this and look up
these scripture verses that support what
we are saying
the bible is now filled with doctrinal
errors nonsense verses grammar errors
new words new people and so forth it's
absolutely heinous
astonishing shocking and absolutely true
so
this is a scripture verse i want to
share with you in acts 13 6
and this is what it says today in the
king james bible this is using blue
letter bible you can do the same thing
and this is the verse today
and when they had gone through the isle
into paphos
i only know a patmose i don't know an
isle of paphos but anyway
they found a certain sorcerer
a false prophet
a jew
whose name was
bar jesus
that's right
bar
jesus
and when we click on g 1919
we discover the following about who this
character is
kjv translates strong's number g 1919 to
bar jesus only one time
he's the son of jesus do you see that
bar jesus a son
of jesus
he's a certain false prophet now in the
bible first i've ever heard of him in my
life
and now we see that he is the son of
jesus
now
we do know and as i've shared with you
that we have
several new
changes to scripture
including this right here
there's more than one jesus in the bible
in fact there are three different
jesus's in
the bible
as we speak
strong's number g 2424 translates
the word to jesus 972 times
jesus or joshua twice
and jesus justice one time
outline of biblical usage
jesus equals jehovah is salvation
jesus the son of god the savior of
mankind
god incarnate
jesus barabbas
was a captive robber whom the jews
begged pilate to release
instead of christ
that's right jesus barabbas
joshua was the famous captain of the
israelites moses successor
jesus
son of lizier one of the ancestors of
christ
and jesus surnamed justice a jewish
christian
an associate with paul in the preaching
of the gospel well right here it
actually looks like we have one two
three four
five different jesus i said three
but they're actually five
different
jesuses
in the bible absolutely astonishing
these are all new
we are finding new people in the bible
we find spelling errors and doctrinal
errors and nonsense verses and grammar
errors
modern words and words omitted
from the bible it's time to wake up in
jesus name
our bibles are under savage attack
as well as the concordance
as well as the vines expository
dictionary
and of course our bible across
translations
and languages across the earth
it's time to get right with jesus christ
do you know jesus christ the word of god
jesus christ is the word of god and we
are to worship him
in spirit and in truth
the bible is a book published by men
you will not be able to take the bible
to heaven with you because it's not
eternal do you understand
the word of god is eternal
but the bible is not eternal
it's time to wake up in jesus name